make anywhere from a thousand to a
thousand five hundred dollars a week as
you begin using a simple strategy Mass
layoff in the United States U.S
inflation like never seen before the
global debt to the highest it's ever
been the economic crisis on the edge of
crashing according to all these news it
is very unlikely for you to have this
type of result however what if I told
you there is a simple way how to
identify whether price is going to go up
or if price is going to go down so you
can capitalize off of these moves make
hundreds thousands if not even hundreds
of thousands of dollars in just a couple
of minutes a day without being an expert
in finance or have any knowledge in the
financial industry or even risk your own
money this is what I call the most
profitable skill ever
[Music]
this opportunity allows anyone to
achieve results anywhere from four
thousand to six thousand dollars every
single month for example Alec born in
France and raised in the United States
where he came to United States speaking
little to no English he was working
paycheck to paycheck not knowing what he
was going to do with little to any
knowledge now he has received over fifty
thousand dollars in just under three
months using my simple simple strategy
now let me ask you a question how good
would it feel for you to be able to
generate anywhere from a thousand to a
thousand five hundred dollars a week
using my simple set and forget strategy
and even more important do you think you
could achieve it in one to two months
for example like Adrian 17 years old
dropped out of high school without
knowing what he was going to do parents
immigrants from Cuba is now generating
over ten thousand dollars a month using
my simple strategy he's the first person
in his family to achieve this type of
success and in the following minutes I'm
going to show you how a 22 year old with
immigrant parents want from working at
Dunkin Donuts just five years ago to
enjoy results just like these
[Music]
but I want to be very clear with this
that doesn't mean that you're going to
have results just like these as soon as
you start at the end of the day I had to
work extremely hard put endless hours
and effort into this all by myself
however I can tell you people like
Felipe Fernando and Alejandro from
Puerto Rico have been able to do it as
well even people from Latin America with
little to no resources working eight
hours a day and earning less than two
thousand dollars a month with zero
experience in this industry have managed
to fully take on the most profitable
skill ever if they can do it in third
world countries so can you all you need
access to is a computer Wi-Fi and a
simple strategy to follow then you have
everything you need to achieve it
because it was the only thing that the
people I have just shown you and myself
that I have used to enjoy the type of
results you're seeing today in this
video I'm going to show you how to make
money in the financial markets how
anyone can achieve it in three months or
less what is the exact stress strategy
that makes me anywhere from forty to
eighty thousand dollars a week that
anybody can replicate how to only take
out one hour out of your day and not
give up on your current job or any of
your studies how you will be able to
avoid risking your own money so you are
totally risk-free and most importantly
why it's the best business model and the
best skill for you to learn so you can
better your life as soon as possible and
why it's the best business model and the
best skill set to learn so you can make
money in your life and to show you all
of this is as legit as it gets I'm going
to show you results of me literally
manifesting that I'm going to make a
hundred thousand dollars in a week my
two hundred thousand dollars that I've
made in a month and well over half a
million dollars that I have made in one
quarter all of this I literally post on
my Instagram telegram Discord YouTube
everything I show you guys and I am as
transparent and legit as it can get but
before I tell you exactly what this is I
want to tell you what it's not it's not
a pyramid scheme it's not not a scam
it's not too late to start it is
definitely not the same thing as Bitcoin
and it is most definitely not the same
thing as stocks absolutely nothing to do
with any of those that I just mentioned
anyone can learn it and start with as
little as 100 you can trade whenever you
want if you want the markets are
literally open 24 5 not like the stock
market that it's from nine to five
Monday through Friday so you can still
have a full-time job and perfect the
craft whenever you want you have way
more leverage and freedom with your
money than any other platform with as
little as 100 with leveraging buying
power your 100 is able to be used as ten
thousand dollars you have way more
leverage and freedom with your money
than any stock or option meaning that
you can start with as little as a
hundred dollars and with leverage your
hundred dollars has a buying power of
one thousand up to ten thousand dollars
obviously depending what leverage you
pick so your hundred dollars was a
really really really long way you can
literally trade from anywhere in the
world and don't need a license to do so
and truthfully just to be honest this is
the easiest way to make a ton of
money and fast and all of this is thanks
to how the market works let me just
explain to you very briefly how it works
the market is consisted of buyers versus
sellers whenever the market is open
market is where one person buying the
other person selling pretty simple right
well thanks to this the market is
created out by supply and demand this
supply and demand is actually seen in
the markets with supply and demand zones
which is very simple but a little more
on this later on in the video but what
does all of this have to do with the
most profitable skill ever well actually
a lot because this is how you earn money
when you learn to identify the supply
and demand zones whether it is
identifying for buyers to buy with them
or sellers to sell with them you will
need to do absolutely nothing else to
make money with the skill it's that
simple the trend is your friend but this
will make more sense later and how do
you lose on the other hand those who
lose money do because they do not know
how to correctly identify the buyers or
sellers or how do you even properly Zone
up supply and demand zones and this is
something that can be learned and
replicated by anybody take Charles he is
fully retired and after his retirement
he ended up deciding he wants to learn a
new skill set to apply and just make
extra money with all of his free time
now Charles is making more money from
Trading than his whole entire retirement
pension that is paying him this is
showing you that you are never too late
to get started trading and anybody can
do it and anybody can replicate it and
to achieve this you don't need to be an
expert in finance have a degree be an
expert in mathematics be on top of the
news articles all day or even be in
front of the computer all day there's a
very very misconception of all of it all
you need is your computer a hundred
dollars to get your first account
started anywhere from one to two hours a
day to study the markets and trade and
most importantly a winning strategy for
example my strategy it allows anybody
that Masters it to make anywhere from a
thousand to a thousand five hundred
dollars a week as a beginner using my
set and forget strategy my strategy is
called set and forget and it is based
off of three simple pillars and the
pillars are based off of the strategy
itself set and forget let me explain set
you up with the proper foundation so you
truly understand all of the trading
principles the vocabulary the trading
tools and everything that will create
the proper foundation so you find these
high probability trade setups and after
you understand that you're ready to
master the top-down analysis time frame
correlations my secret areas of Interest
with supply and demand along with entry
signal and risk management and then you
can forget about going back to work or
having to watch any other educational
videos because here we teach you how to
scale your account and how to truly be
fully in control of all of your emotions
and how to master your psychology and
how to manage your trades so you don't
fail and continue succeeding if you're
able to understand and dominate these
three pillars earning money is the last
of your worries just how it was for my
top Trader HD which he asked me to keep
his identity private because he works
for the government he just says that
it's better which I've tried to get him
on several podcasts but he just doesn't
accept it where he is generating well
over fifty thousand dollars a month
using my set and forget strategy coming
from a corporate job he is still working
that corporate job and on top of that
generating over fifty thousand dollars
using my seven forget strategy now the
question is is it really worth it for
you to get started in this business
model you can start with with as little
as a hundred dollars and with those
hundred dollars you can have the buying
power of ten thousand dollars and grow
your account very very fast you can only
trade wherever you want the markets are
open 24 five even 24 7 if you want to
trade cryptos yes my strategy works on
cryptos as well once profitable you can
get endless amounts of investors freedom
of not having to deal with anybody other
than yourself and the computer in other
Industries you have clients you have
product issues you have marketing you
have ads you have uh stock inventory
here it is literally just you a computer
and some Wi-Fi and it's the fastest way
to scale your net worth and get results
meanwhile with other vehicles it's
actually the quite opposite like Amazon
Bitcoin Airbnb or social media agency
marketing I would not recommend those to
anybody even less to start as a beginner
I personally try to myself Airbnb
property manager me I personally tried
Amazon Drop Shipping and Amazon FBA and
for me I had no results let me actually
show you these in a much more graphic
way decided to do is create this chart
and show you the difference between the
most profitable skill ever and the other
companies that I highly don't recommend
let's start off with Amazon so Amazon
you need a starting capital of five
thousand dollars your margins are
anywhere from 15 to 30 percent meaning
that whatever you sell let's say you
sell a thousand dollar product your
margins are anywhere from 15 to 30 so
you would probably just make 150 bucks
to three hundred dollars Max and selling
a thousand dollar product through Amazon
is is quite a lot what do you need to
start to earn money well actually a lot
in order for you to start earning money
on Amazon you need to have an account
you have to have a product you have to
have a supplier you have to take care of
the logistics you need to have a winning
listing strategy and you need to be on
top of the inventory you need to have
have customer support you need to have
good trust party reviews there's just a
lot that goes into Amazon because you're
you're selling a product and you need to
make sure the product comes good from
your vendor there's a lot that goes into
this I probably wasted a total of six
months on this and saw little to even
negative results so what do you need in
order to succeed to this you need to be
responsible for the suppliers in China
you have to have winning products which
is probably one of the most tricky Parts
because you don't know what products are
going to be winning and you need to be
able to find products that are high in
demand so you can figure out how you're
going to sell them so you need to
compete with the people that are already
selling whatever product the risk
associated are extremely high they're
high due to the depending on how much
you stock they're high because delivery
times can take a long time for you to
get your product you depend on platform
blockages the effectiveness of ads you
can get blocked by Facebook or even
customers that end up disputing or
saying that they never got the product
so the risk associated with this is
extremely high and the scalability isn't
really are there because scaling your
storage would depend on the winning
products ranging from viral or even
seasonal and as soon as your product is
going viral another one comes out or a
competitor just beats your margins or
it's just not in the season anymore so
Works only for certain times of the year
and besides you're really limited to to
only a certain amount of stock because
once your supplier in China or for
wherever they are they run out you're
pretty much out of business so for me
Amazon is not an ideal business at all
next we have Bitcoin so Bitcoin you can
start from anywhere from a thousand to
ten thousand dollars whatever
realistically you have available to you
your margins are great because you keep
a hundred percent of the profits
obviously the four tax what do you need
to earn the money realistically nothing
you just need to figure out how you're
going to get this money and just put it
into Bitcoin what do you need in order
to succeed well realistically you need
to have a winning strategy if you're
holding Bitcoin obviously over a long
time you need to make sure you're
anywhere in the world where the
government does not ban any of the other
cryptos and you have to make sure you
need to have a high level of security so
they don't hack your cryptos and the
risk associated with this are actually
very high you guys have seen endless of
exchanges going out of business so you
realistically don't know if your money
is safe and the good part about this is
that the scalability is high because
obviously you know if you have more
money under management you earn more
money doing the same thing but they're
just just realistically a lot of risk
because you don't know when Bitcoin is
going to hit 100K 200k so it's more of
like an investment long-term play versus
a day-to-day weekly or even a monthly
thing next we have Airbnb so this is
actually one of the most difficult ones
that I personally experience myself
because you need anywhere from 5 000 to
100 000 dollars just to get started next
your margins are anywhere from 15 to 40
percent on the extremely high end on a
good good month because it is anything
from what you obviously rent out that
month what do you need to start to earn
money with this and there's actually
quite a lot that goes into it so to
start off you need to get your own house
or you need to do a rental Arbitrage you
need to make sure you're at a short-term
rental Zone because you're not then you
get fined you need to remodel take the
pictures post it make sure you're on top
of the reviews have fast and A1
communication have the keys easy access
for the tenants so once they get there
they just put the code and get in you
need to have the customer support on
point there's just a lot that you need
to do in order to start earning money
with this what do you need in order to
succeed in this most importantly and
realistically it's more than you can
imagine because you have to manage the
properties you need to make sure that
you're in a good location you need to
make sure that it leaves you with a
margin you have to make sure that you're
competing with the other Airbnb listings
you need to make sure that there's a
team that manages it correctly you have
to guess have to make sure there's a
team uh following up with the Canadian
lady like I actually have a very funny
story with the clingy ladies and it is I
got a message at three in the morning
from one of the attendants that was
staying at the Airbnb that I was uh
rental arbit charging and they asked me
at three in the morning where can they
find more towels after all of the ones
are dirty and they ended up blowing up
my phone and leaving a bad review
because there was an extra towels after
they used up over 20 sets of towels from
the pool and then they blamed us for it
because there wasn't any more clean
towels so there's just so much that goes
into it in order for you to have it's in
order for you to succeed there's a lot
of patience that needs to be implemented
what are the risks Associated and the
risks are actually pretty high because
you need to make sure that the
renovations are there here you have to
make sure that the contractors are doing
the wall job when they're repairing for
anything that the attendants break you
got to make sure that the clean ladies
are doing their job there's just a lot
of risks that go with it and the
scalability is actually very low because
there's a lot of regulators going in on
it there's a lot of competition in this
space and realistically a lot of
homeowners do this just to use it as a
vacation home that pays for itself when
you try to turn Airbnb rental Arbitrage
into a business it is not that high
because a lot of people that just own
let's say beach homes or vacation homes
instead of them just paying that
mortgage monthly and it being a loss for
them they just rent it out enough to
cover the mortgage and that's it so they
basically have it for free so when you
try to create a business you're going
against the people that just want to
cover the mortgage so competing with the
prices is very very very hard next we
have social media marketing agency so
this you actually need 0 need to start
so this is probably one of the most
attractive ones because you need
absolutely no money your margins are
anywhere from 30 to 60 percent so they
are about the third to highest on this
chart right here and what you need to
start to earn money is actually a lot
more than you can imagine because what
you mainly need is you need to define a
niche to help people so first you need
to have a strategy to be able to help
people you need to have you proven you
need to have a proven marketing strategy
that works you need to have a team of
professionals who can deliver run the
ads learn how to run the ads a team to
create the creatives clients with a
proven marketing strategy that works so
you need to obviously have testimonials
and you need to do it for yourself so
then you can do it so you can do it for
other people well you need in order to
succeed in this is actually even more
than you can imagine you need to master
Facebook marketing you need to have
customers that listen and trust in you
because you can be surprised is how
people will hire you to run ads and then
they will tell you how to run their own
ads meaning that they have no trust and
the companies need to have very good
quality clients you need to have a good
team to make sure all of the ads are on
top of the a game and you make sure that
your offer is actually attractive for
your clients the risk associated with
this are high as well simply because the
blockages of advertising platforms
Facebook is constantly giving you
reasons to stop pushing your ads your
team can either get tired of being on
top of stuff and then they just simply
quit and then unstable customers pretty
much changing the plans and the
strategies of what you guys originally
started with because they're not
patients with the results so it's just
constantly back and forth and you know
with clients and figuring out how to
keep them happy the scalability with
this is actually low to medium because
truthfully it's you versus the client
getting them to understand as long as
your equipment and your marketing is
good you can scale it but this can take
years to perfect and be in very very
very good relationship with your
customers and be on top of the a game
with Facebook and the ads and then
lastly the most profitable skill ever it
has the second best attractive starting
Capital anywhere from a hundred to one
thousand dollars the margins are 100
everything you make you absolutely keep
what do you need in order to start
earning money it is literally nothing
all you need is a winning strategy like
my set and forget you need to have an
account with a hundred dollars minimum
and Wi-Fi on your phone or computer
that's all you need and these are stuff
that we all have every single day access
to what do you need in order to succeed
on this well realistically it's just one
thing all you need is a winning strategy
once you have a winning strategy that's
it that's all you need in order to
succeed what are the risks associated
with this the risks are actually lower
than you can imagine because once you
understand how to properly manage your
money all of the risks are completely
eliminated you will never lose money
ever again that's exactly what I teach
how to properly manage your money and
the scalability let me tell you right
now it is the highest of this chart
because you just need to make more money
to scale so once you start earning 1 000
then you start earning 10 000 and I
almost guarantee you 100K weeks and
months would just come over time at this
point it would be a good idea to ask
yourself if all this would work for you
because it is more than clear that it
actually works just as it worked for
Clem he literally came next to me after
being in this industry for three years
and not having any Clarity and being
totally lost with what to do on his
day-to-day basis after he applied my
simple seven figure strategy he is not
only now having results but his Clarity
is better than ever and now he knows
exactly what to do every single morning
when he wakes up and he comes to his
computer so he can capitalize off of the
moves every single day or even Kaden
that he has sent me two video
testimonials excited with joy thanking
me for how much effort and how simple I
made the center forget strategy videos
that now he has total Clarity and with
just four months into his trading
Journey he has a very clear indication
of where to buy where to sell and how to
properly manage his money while this is
the best option to start as a beginner
and why this will work for you first I'm
going to explain to you how to not lose
money this is very simple to not lose
money with the most profitable skill
ever you must follow the plan on how
much money you're going to risk per
transaction versus how much money you're
going to gain this way every single
trade every single loss is 100 perfectly
calculated not leaving you with any
doubt with how much money is going to be
left on the table so you are 100 in
control and never never ever ever lose
more than what you're okay with risking
next we have how much time would it take
for me to learn and earn money and this
truly depends on the amount of time and
effort the person dedicates to learning
and you dedicate anywhere from one to
three hours every single day in a matter
of three months you will be able to
generate anywhere from a thousand to a
thousand five hundred dollars a week as
a beginner using my setting for guest
strategy however I have cases like
dutches that she has had results in
record time she is a female Trader from
London and she is actually one of my
first female Traders students ever that
has been able to have these type of
results in little to almost under three
months next is Will trading really work
for me trading can really be done for
any person realistically it could be
anywhere from a person working at Dunkin
Donuts or any fast food chain all the
way up to a doctor or a person working
at the government like my student HD or
a person that is retired and that has
all the free time in the world to master
in your craft the only thing you have to
do to make it work for you is commit
commit to the process where I'm really
going to give you my set and forget
strategy for you to succeed if you
follow it it is literally impossible to
not get results let's say right now I
tell you go to the gym every single day
for the next three months and hit 500
sit-ups every single day it is literally
impossible for you to not have abs by
the end of the three months with
obviously following proper diet it is
the same thing with my set and forget
strategy all you have to do is commit it
is impossible for you to not get results
if you truly commit one to two hours
every single day next is know when to
buy know when to sell and know when to
do nothing which is very important and
one of the things that I like the most
about the most profitable skill ever is
that I'd say probably about 90 of the
time I am totally still I'm do doing
nothing to make money in the world all
you have to do is just create certain
rules you will only do something when
the set and forget strategy allows you
to do it and 90 of the time is waiting
for that right trade setup to come so
then you take it it's like you're just
they're standing in home base waiting
for that Perfect Pitch once that Perfect
Pitch comes down that line you just bat
it and you get that home run and that's
how we managed to get these big trades
and generate anywhere from a thousand to
a thousand five hundred dollars every
single week also a doubt is what if you
don't have any money to start well
realistically all you really need is
just a hundred dollars that is all you
need to get your first account open for
you to be able to use leverage and start
learning how to manage money but however
let's say you don't want to scale your
100 account to a bigger account there
are firms out there looking for
profitable Traders with a good strategy
like rocket21 that are allowing you to
manage up to 600 000 right off the bat
so realistically money realistic
basically isn't an issue with you
because either you can start with a
hundred dollars or there's firms out
there that will fund you and you keep
anywhere from 80 to 90 of the money you
make on your account all you have to do
is just pass the challenge and if you
show them they're profitable they can
fund you 25 50 100K and like I said up
to 600 000 with rocket 21. and with
three months of consistent profits like
50 of my students you can even have up
to one million dollars with their
scaling account which is five I already
explained to you how you can do all this
but however now I wanted to see if
you're able to do it or not and for that
in a short summary I'm going to show you
how you can achieve these type of
results in less than three months with
just a laptop of phone and some Wi-Fi
such as Joseph and Mateo which they both
came to me not understanding absolutely
how to read the market structure at all
and after watching all of the videos not
only do they have Clarity on how to read
the markets but they read it just how I
you so every single week they're
analyzing the markets without me being
there besides the fact that I'm there
with them every single Sunday guiding
them on which markets for them to be
trading they do it on their own which is
the most important part because now they
can do this from anywhere in the world
with just Wi-Fi and a computer so now
let's see how by applying these three
pillars at the same time you can make
anywhere from a thousand to a thousand
five hundred dollars a week using my
simple seven figure strategy so let me
show you guys in the market exactly what
I mean summarized very simply so step
one first thing we do when we get to the
market is where is the market headed is
the market headed to the upside or is it
headed to the downside which is simple
analogy that I like to use is a wave
analogy let's say you're a surfer the
first thing you do as a surfer when you
get to the beach is you want to identify
what ways are the waves going are the
waves going to the East are the waves
going to the West because your goal is
to get on the wave and just ride it all
the way to the shore so as you can tell
here when you get to the beach are the
waves going this way are the waves going
this way are they going down the middle
because your goal is to ride the wave
with it not against it so in this case
the waves would be going west this case
the waves would be going east so this is
the first we're going to do when we come
to the market in this case are the waves
heading to the upside or are the waves
going to the downside as you can tell
this is very similar
this Market structure to how the waves
move so in this example right here this
would be the waves going to the upside
this would be the waves going to the
downside so this would be us right here
riding on top of the wave this is a you
know perfect figure of us on a wave
heading up and this is us on a wave
heading to the downside so all our goal
when we come to the market is to
understand are the waves going up so we
get on the waves going to the upside as
a buyer or are the waves heading down so
we enter the waves to the downside as a
center we want to be a surfer and we
want to surf the wave in the direction
that it is going so in this market right
here the first thing that we could
identify is that these waves are clearly
going to the upside so after we
identified that the market is going up
or down which in this case the market is
going up then we lead to our second
point which is where are we buying and
where are we selling which in the case
of Surfing would be be where are we
entering in the wave so now that we
understand that the wave is going to the
east side now we're going to enter the
waves to the east side obviously because
our goal as a surfer is to ride the wave
all the way to the shore so in this case
now that we understand that we're going
up is where do we enter and we want to
enter obviously before the wave takes
golf because we want to ride the wave we
don't we don't want to enter the wave
too high because then we fall off we
don't want to enter too low because then
we don't end up riding the wave it's the
same thing in the market you don't want
to enter in a move way too low because
then you essentially could miss the
whole entire trade or you don't want to
enter too high because then you can miss
the trade so after we understand where
we've got on the waiver where we got on
the trade is where are we going to get
out we obviously understand we can't
ride the wave past the shoreline but you
know some Surfers they can by the way
I'm not a surfer myself I'm just saying
these analogies but I know some servers
might want to ride the you know wave
past the shorthand or whatever but in
trading this is very common Traders
don't know when to get out so after we
understand that the market is heading up
where we're buying it then we got to
know where we're getting out before the
trade pulls back and takes us out on a
loss and this is very important because
this is where we lock in our profits so
we basically set our take profit zones
on the time frame that we are buying so
let's say that we are on a wave and we
got it let's say in the middle of the
shoreline we ride it all the way to the
sand they're halfway to the sand but
basically as you have an objective of
where you are going to get out you need
to know exactly where you're getting out
right as you get in and this is all part
of this set and forget strategy there is
a plan behind every single trade the
whole entire way next comes a very key
point for experienced Traders anywhere
from three to eight months and that is
how to manage a trade while you're in it
and not lose money and surfing analogy
is how to manage to stay surfboard and
not fall because I don't know if any of
you guys have surfed before but once you
get on that wave and you essentially
start feeling the pressure it is very
easy to kind of slip off so it's how do
you stay on that surfboard so you ride
all the way to the shore and you don't
fall off and this is part of our trade
management this is part of our position
sizing this is part of our Oso risk
management that was taken behind the
trade and this is crucial to your
trading or crucial to your surfing
because if you don't do this the right
way as soon as you get onto that wave on
the surfboard you can slip off due to
pressure same thing when it comes to the
trade as soon as you get into the trade
you can close too early and not maximize
those profits because the pressure gets
to you or just the money gets to your
head so this is very key in what I teach
and lastly which I personally think it's
one of the most important parts and has
the most value that is keeping you
accountable to keep doing the same thing
because once you start winning you start
making money you can tend to get a
little sloppy or forget the strategy to
put it into terms of surf thing is how
to respect the ocean and not take it for
granted because once you start learning
how to surf you can probably start
wanting to do tricks you can start
getting into these big waves and then
this is where you can maybe get yourself
into a lot of trouble because this is
where Traders get too confident and they
start over risking and they just start
doing things they're not supposed to do
so in terms of Surfing this would be
where you can do tricks on the waves or
you can go into too much in the deep end
you get eaten by a shark or just fall
off the wave and get hurt so this is
where I do every single week a call with
everybody that joins the setting forget
strategy team and then I hold you
accountable and keep mentoring you so
you follow the strategy and stick to the
plan every single week because that type
of accountability is what keeps you in
check to keep making anywhere from a
thousand to a thousand five hundred
dollars a week without breaking any of
the rules if you believe you can carry
out these simple actions that I showed
you you will be able to generate
anywhere from eight to twelve percent
every single month I don't know if this
sounds good to you but I'm going to show
you some projections so you can see how
much money you can make with spending
anywhere from one to two hours a day in
front of your computer remember you can
achieve these results with a funded
account risking none of your money as I
just explained to you a couple minutes
ago now I'm going to show you the same
percentage what it looks like on
different account sizes once you're
funded let's put three scenarios first
scenario is you have a twenty five
thousand dollar account you risk one
percent per trade and every single trade
you win you win three percent so let's
say you have a 50 50 win rate so out of
10 trades you win five and you lose five
so out of ten trades you lose five but
then you win five so you lose five
trades at one percent but every single
trade you win you win at three percent
that leaves you with a total net profits
of 10 after making back the five percent
of losses you had so you had five wins
five losses and you're still up 10 on
your twenty five thousand dollar account
giving you a two thousand five hundred
dollar profit let's take the same
scenario on a 50k account you risk one
percent per trade and every single trade
you win you win three percent with a
fifty fifty percent win rate on the
strategy let's say you lose five trades
and let's say you win five every single
trade you lose you lose one percent
every single trade you win you win three
percent after winning two trades in a
row you make back for those five losses
and everything after that is straight
profit leaving you with again ten
percent in profit ten percent on a 50k
account is now five thousand dollars but
let's take this same account onto a
hundred thousand dollars so let's say
you risk one percent on every trade you
take and every single trade you win you
win three percent let's say your win
rate is a 50 50 so every single trade
lose five trades and then you win five
trades so every single trade you lose is
one percent so that is a total of five
percent and every single trade you win
is a total of three percent leaving you
with a total of fifteen percent after
you make back for those five percent
losses you are left with a total of ten
percent in profit and that was ten
percent on a hundred K account which is
very easy to get funded at rocket21 that
is a total of ten thousand dollars in
one month with very very simple risk
management just risking one percent of
your account can get any easier than
that and this is why people like Kim
making over a thousand seven hundred
dollars a day from just using the simple
strategy he went from being negative to
now making all of the money back that he
lost on just using these simple risk
management with my strategy you went
from not knowing nothing to now
withdrawing from the markets every
single week and just like one of my OG
students Andrew Lizzy he was one of my
first students to access to my seven
figure strategy and he went from being a
consistently lost Trader to now
receiving multiple past accounts
multiple funded accounts and getting
multiple payouts so all I have to say is
if if I went from Dunkin Donuts working
at the fair working at the mall and
losing over thirty thousand dollars in
my first two years of trading and I am
able to have these type of results today
so can you all I have to say is if you
would have met me five years ago I would
have asked you what type of sugar and
how much cream you want in your coffee
and what type of donut do you want for
breakfast I've literally gone from
Dunkin Donuts to working at the fair
working at the mall to then joining
these pyramid schemes and trading
figuring out how to piece these random
Youtube Forex strategies together to now
having results like this this was all
with endless endless hours and effort of
trading being put every single day over
the course course of five years there
was a point where I was negative thirty
thousand dollars on my second year of
trading but everything literally clicked
everything literally turned once on that
second year and a half when I stuck to
my strategy and I had fully perfected it
and stuck to it consistently for three
months then I started having hundred
dollar weeks then I started having
thousand dollar weeks ten thousand
dollar months ten thousand dollar weeks
and the snowball just got bigger bigger
and bigger so it got to the point where
I just had my biggest trading day for
000 and my biggest trading month for
over three hundred thousand dollars in
one single month and once you start
making all of this money it's kind of
like GTA once you pass all of the
missions you kind of just have nothing
else to do like you basically beat the
game you're you know now you're you're
pretty much rich like you just go have
fun now and drive super cars that's
basically what it is now but instead of
me just driving super cars and just
being bored all day I'm giving back to
the community I'm of you guys just saw
but I just gave away my Lamborghini to
people that did Rock Paper Scissors at
an event here in Miami I'm always giving
away challenges I'm always giving money
away to the people that are hard workers
I'm always constantly giving back and
now I'm giving you my set and forget
strategy so you can do the same thing as
me because it's going to help you to
gain anywhere from a thousand to a
thousand five hundred dollars a week as
a beginner Forex Trader using my Center
forget strategy all this you've already
seen is simple but simple doesn't mean
easy so if you want these to be results
go to the link in the description and I
have a video for you there that is going
to help you gain these results in under
three months same as it did for all the
people that I showed you in this video
Once you watch the video all the way to
the end everything is going to have so
much more clarity and it's going to be
so much more in-depth than this video
right here everything is in the link in
the description below where I'm going to
teach you how to have the same results
as I did but most importantly in record
time you watch this video all the way to
the end big thank you make sure to hit
that like And subscribe button because I
have many many many more great videos
coming out and most importantly whenever
you're in doubt make sure to set and
forget and I'll see you guys in the next
video take it easy guys